Stereographic Cards
Marist Archives and Special Collections
- Stereographic Cards, 2.1.8
  - Verso: The Taj Mahal, Agra, India: The Taj Mahal (t j ma-h l ) is one of the most beautiful temples in the world. It stands in a garden on the banks..., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 18-verso (Box 1609)
  - Most Gigantic Defensive Work in the World Great Wall of China on Rugged Hills Near Nankow Pass., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 19 (Box 1609)
  - Verso: The Great Wall of China on the Rugged Hills near Nankow Pass: This is a part of the ancient barrier set up by the Chinese two thousand, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 19-verso (Box 1609)
  - One of the Loveliest Spots in India Kiosk-bordered Tank at Ulwar., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 20 (Box 1609)
  - Verso: One of the Loveliest Spots in India Kiosk-bordered Tank at Ulwar: This is in the heart of one of the proudest principalities of Rajputana, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 20-verso (Box 1609)
  - Devout Mohammedans Prostrate at Prayer Time Jama Masiid, India's Greatest Mosque, Delhi., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 21 (Box 1609)
  - Verso: Mohammedans at Prayer Time Jama Masjid, Delhi, India: That building at the left of the great court, with its pointed domes and the, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 21-verso (Box 1609)
  - The Glittering Pomp of the East the Great Durbar Procession, Delhi, India., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 22 (Box 1609)
  - Verso: The Great Durbar Procession, Delhi, India: Never since the western world has known the ceremonial pomp of Indian magnates has, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 22-verso (Box 1609)
  - Inflated Bullock Skins for Ferry Boats on Sutlej River in the Punjab, India., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 23 (Box 1609)
  - Verso: Inflated Bullock Skins for Ferry Boats on Sutlej River in the Punjab, India: If you look at this view carefully you will wonder why it is named, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 23-verso (Box 1609)
  - An Earthly Paradise Famous Vale of Kashmir Watered by the Winding Jhelum, India., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 24 (Box 1609)
  - Verso: Famous Vale of Kashmir Watered by the Winding Jhelum, India: The Valley of Kashmir in the mountainous region to the north of India, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 24-verso (Box 1609)
  - Shelling Rice, and Gossiping with the Neighbors Home Life of Contented Citizens of Kashmir., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 25 (Box 1609)
  - Verso: Shelling Rice, and Gossiping with the Neighbors Home Life of Kashmir Citizens, India: It is the home of a family of average working, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 25-verso (Box 1609)
  - Spinning and Weaving Woolen Shawls, Srinagar, Kashmir, India., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 26 (Box 1609)
  - Verso: Manufacturing Woolen Shawls, Srinagar, Kashmir, India: In this view you behold an ancient civilization. Some of our famous scholars, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 26-verso (Box 1609)
  - "The Roof of the World" the Majestic Himalayas, Northern India., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 27 (Box 1609)
  - Verso: The Majestic Himalayas, Northern India: The word "Himalayas" means the "abode of snow". The mountains are well named, as the, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 27-verso (Box 1609)
  - A Burning Ghat on the Banks of the Sacred Ganges, Benares, India., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 28 (Box 1609)
  - Verso: Burning Ghat on Banks of Sacred Ganges, Benares, India: You are looking from the deck of a riverboat similar to those now lying at, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 28-verso (Box 1609)
  - Sacred Hindu Cattle on the Street, Calcutta, India., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 29 (Box 1609)
  - Verso: Sacred Cattle Wandering on Sidewalks and in Streets, Calcutta, India: This view shows a city street in Calcutta, India. Here the native, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 29-verso (Box 1609)
  - Jain Temple, Richest Place of Worship in Calcutta, India., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 30 (Box 1609)
  - Verso: Jain Temple, Richest Place of Worship in Calcutta, India: This is one of the most magnificent temples in all India. It was built by a single, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 30-verso (Box 1609)
  - North Section of the "450 Pagodas." Each Enshrining a Book of Wisdom. Mandalay, Burma., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 31 (Box 1609)
  - Verso: North Section of the "450 Pagodas," Mandalay, Burma: Here in "Golden Mandalay" we are 21 degrees north of the equator, in the southern, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 31-verso (Box 1609)
  - Giant Beasts of Burden Elephants Hauling Teak Logs from Salwin River, Maulmain, Burma., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 32 (Box 1609)
  - Verso: Elephants Hauling Teak Logs from Salwin River, Maulmain, Burma: Burma is that part of India that lies in the Indo-China peninsula east, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 32-verso (Box 1609)
  - Royal Elephant Hunt, Siam., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 33 (Box 1609)
  - Verso: Royal Elephant Hunt, Siam: How would you like to go hunting for elephants? If you should go on such a hunt in Africa, it would be to, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 33-verso (Box 1609)
  - Looking Across the Bay of Kowloon to Hong Kong and Victoria Peak, China., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 34 (Box 1609)
  - Verso: Hong Kong and Victoria Peak from Kowloon, China: The bay of Kowloon, through which we here see an ocean steamer passing out to, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 34-verso (Box 1609)
  - The Chukiang River with Its Enormous Floating Popoulation, Canton, China., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 35 (Box 1609)
  - Verso: The Chukiang River at Canton, China: We are looking directly east in the heart of the city of Canton, in southeastern China. Most of, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 35-verso (Box 1609)
  - A Modern Metropolis of the Orient The Bund, Shanghai, China., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 36 (Box 1609)
  - Verso: The Bund and the Whangpoo River, Shanghai, China: We are looking north over Shanghai from the Typhoon Tower, used by the Weather Bureau, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 36-verso (Box 1609)
  - Where a Famous Oriental Love Story was Born, Shanghai, China., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 37 (Box 1609)
  - Verso: The Willow Pattern Tea House, Shanghai, China: Since the days when the tall-masted East Indiamen sailed around the Horn, or beat down, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 37-verso (Box 1609)
  - A River Scene of Today in the Picturesque Land of Confucious, China., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 38 (Box 1609)
  - Verso: The Picturesque Land of Confucius River Life in China: Before us is a scene typical, at least near the seaboard, of the transitional condtions, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 38-verso (Box 1609)
  - The Yangtze River Valley at Chinkiang, China., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 39 (Box 1609)
  - Verso: The Yangtze River, Chinkiang, China: The Yangtze (y ng tse ) is the third longest river system in the world. The Mississippi-Missouri ranks, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 39-verso (Box 1609)
  - Primitive Lumber, Sawing in Peiping, China., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 40 (Box 1609)
  - Verso: Sawing Lumber by Hand in a Lumber yard on the Outskirts of Peiping, China: In China there are no great forest from which to make lumber, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 40-verso (Box 1609)
  - The Pomp and Pageantry of a Chinese Funeral, Peiping, China., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 41 (Box 1609)
  - Verso: A Chinese Funeral in the Streets of Peiping, China: Peiping, until 1928 known to the world as Peking, fascinating focus of the mystery and, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 41-verso (Box 1609)
  - In the City of Kuhlai Ha-ta-Men Street, Peiping, China., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 42 (Box 1609)
  - Verso: Looking from the Tartar City into Chinese City, South from Ha-ta-Men Gate, Peiping: Though fallen, for the time being, upon evil days, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 42-verso (Box 1609)
  - Picturesque Chinese Junk under Full Sail on the Yellow Sea, Coast of Manchuria in Distance., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 43 (Box 1609)
  - Verso: Chinese Junk under Full Sail on Yellow Sea: To the north, directly beyond the swelling sails of this primitive craft, lies Manchuria., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 43-verso (Box 1609)
  - Chinese Boys Plowing near Port Arthur, Manchuria., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 44 (Box 1609)
  - Verso: Chinese Boys Plowing near Port Arthur, Manchuria: The Yellow Sea lies between the peninsula of Korea and China. At the northern part, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 44-verso (Box 1609)
  - Busy Street Scene in the Ancient City of the Manchus. Mukden, Manchuria., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 45 (Box 1609)
  - Verso: Street in Ancient City of the Manchus, Mukden, China: Although Mukden has fallen from the high estate which it once had as the capital, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 45-verso (Box 1609)
  - Farm Woman Supervising the Tedious Grinding of a Grain Mill in Manchuria., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 46 (Box 1609)
  - Verso: Farm Woman Supervising Grinding of Grain, Mill in Manchuria: The mule is the Chinese beast of burden, endlessly he revolved the, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 46-verso (Box 1609)
  - Boarding the Train at Kansk, Siberia., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 47 (Box 1609)
  - Verso: Boarding the Train at Kansk, Siberia: Asia is the largest continent on the globe. Three-fifths of the land of the world are in its boundaries., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 47-verso (Box 1609)
  - Pottery Peddlers on the Streets of Seoul, Chosen., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 48 (Box 1609)
  - Verso: Pottery Peddlers on the Streets of Seoul, Korea: A wall extends for fourteen miles around Seoul, the capital, including a good deal of, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 48-verso (Box 1609)
  - Plowing Scene near Seoul a Korean Farmer in his White Costume., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 49 (Box 1609)
  - Verso: Plowing Scene near Seoul, Korea: Korea is about the size of Great Britain or the state of Minnesota. Stretched along our coast in its own, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 49-verso (Box 1609)
  - Before the Earthquake of 1923 Shops and Crowds on a Busy Street of Yokohama, Japan., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 50 (Box 1609)
  - Verso: Shops and Crowds on a Yokohama Business Street, Japan: This Japanese quarter of Yokohama is quite distinct from the district up on, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 50-verso (Box 1609)
  - Before the Earthquake West from Nihonbashi (Bridge), Tokyo, Japan., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 51 (Box 1609)
  - Verso: West from Nihonbashi (Bridge), Tokyo, Japan: This is the east-central part of the great city, the district called Nihonbashi-ku, in which, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 51-verso (Box 1609)
  - All Sorts and Sizes A Japanese Shoe Shop., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 52 (Box 1609)
  - Verso: All Sorts and Sizes A Japanese Shoe Shop: Wearers of clogs claim a sanitary advantage over wearers of shoes. Then clogs have also, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 52-verso (Box 1609)
  - Idyllic Spot Where Japanese Maids Delight to Stroll Manyasu-ro Gardens near Tokyo., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 53 (Box 1609)
  - Verso: A Charming Example of Japanese Landscape Gardening Manyasu-ro Gardens near Tokyo: The Japanese excel all other people in landscape, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 53-verso (Box 1609)
  - Rich and Beautiful Ornamentation of the Great Temple Gate, Nikko, Japan., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 54 (Box 1609)
  - Verso: Beautiful Ornamentation of Great Temple Gate, Nikko: We are nearly a hundred miles from Tokyo among the Nikko mountains at the, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 54-verso (Box 1609)
  - A Street in Mountainous Nikko, a Religious Center of Japan., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 55 (Box 1609)
  - Verso: A Street in Mountainous Nikko, a Religious Center of Japan: The Japanese have a saying which may be translated, "Until you have seen, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 55-verso (Box 1609)
  - Where Intensive Agriculture Is a Necessity Setting Out Rice Plants, Japan., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 56 (Box 1609)
  - Verso: Setting Out Rice Plants, Japan: Here are two families planting rice in their miniature rice-fields. The fields are so tiny that some one has, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 56-verso (Box 1609)
  - A Charming Outlook over Fertile Fields and Cozy Homes at Kiriu, Japan., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 57 (Box 1609)
  - Verso: Outlook Over Fertile Fields and Cozy Homes at Kiriu, Japan: Kiriu is 81 miles by rail north-northwest of Tokyo. It is an important town of, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 57-verso (Box 1609)
  - Feeding Mulberry Leaves to the Voracious Young Silkworms, Japan., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 58 (Box 1609)
  - Verso: Feeding Mulberry Leaves to Silkworms, Japan: Silkworm eggs are hatched in an incubator. The young worms are then taken to a feeding, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 58-verso (Box 1609)
  - The Planet Saturn, Solar Observatory of the Carnegie Institution at Mount Wilson, California., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 59 (Box 1609)
  - Verso: The Planet Saturn and its Rings: This is one of the most beautiful objects in the sky and is unique among the planets. In the telescope, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 59-verso (Box 1609)
  - Beloved of Artists and Poets Snow-capped Fuji, the Sacred Mountain of Japan., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 60 (Box 1609)
  - Verso: Snow-capped Fuji, the Sacred Mountain of Japan: Mount Zion was not more sacred to the Hebrew poets than is this Holw White Mountain, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 60-verso (Box 1609)
  - Two Miles Above the Clouds From Fuji toward Lake Yamanaka, Ten Miles Away, Japan., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 61 (Box 1609)
  - Verso: From Fuji toward Lake Yamanaka, Japan: You are over 12,300 feet above the sea; this slippery, cindery slope below your feet is away, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 61-verso (Box 1609)
  - Natives at a Festival in Jokjakarta, Java., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 62 (Box 1609)
  - Verso: Natives at a Festival in Jokjakarta, Java: Java, the richest island of the East Indies, and most extensively cultivated island in the tropics, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 62-verso (Box 1609)
  - The Full Moon, Yerkes Observatory., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 63 (Box 1609)
  - Verso: The Full Moon: This photograph of the moon shows clearly that the moon is round or, to say it more correctly, the moon is an almost, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 63-verso (Box 1609)
  - The Planet Mars, Yerkes Observatory., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 64 (Box 1609)
  - Verso: The Planet Mars: If you look at the sky on a clear night you will see a countless number of "stars". Some are very bright, others are very, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 64-verso (Box 1609)
  - Morehouse's Comet, Yerkes Observatory., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 65 (Box 1609)
  - Verso: Morehouse's Comet: This is a wonderful view of a comet sweeping across the sky. Formerly these were looked upon as evil omens., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 65-verso (Box 1609)
  - The Sun Photographed through Forty-inch Telescope. Copyright Yerkes Observatory., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 66 (Box 1609)
  - Verso: Photograph of the Sun Made by Yerkes Observatory: The sun is the center of our planetary system. About it the planets move in regular, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 66-verso (Box 1609)
  - Papaya Trees, in the Mauna Loa Valley, Hawaii., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 67 (Box 1609)
  - Verso: Papaya Trees, in the Mauna Loa Valley, Hawaii: The Hawaiian (h -wi yan) islands are of volcanic formation. There are many mountains..., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 67-verso (Box 1609)
  - An American Sugar Mill in the Hawaiian Islands., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 68 (Box 1609)
  - Verso: An American Sugar Mill in the Hawaiian Islands: The cultivation of sugar cane and its manufacture into raw sugar has become within the, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 68-verso (Box 1609)
  - Pineapple Plantation, First and Second Years' Growth, near Honolulu., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 69 (Box 1609)
  - Verso: Pineapple Plantation, First and Second Years' Growth, near Honolulu: A great proportion of the canned pineapple we so much enjoy, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 69-verso (Box 1609)
  - Native Hula Girls in Characteristic Attire near Honolulu, Territory of Hawaii., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 70 (Box 1609)
  - Verso: Native Hula Girls near Honolulu, Hawaii: These are native Hawaiian girl dancers. The hula is one of the ancient dances of the natives., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 70-verso (Box 1609)
  - Government Building, formerly the Royal Palace, Honolulu, Hawaii., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 71 (Box 1609)
  - Verso: Government Building, formerly the Royal Palace, Honolulu, Hawaii: Many exciting incidents have marked the history of the building, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 71-verso (Box 1609)
  - Mission Home Grounds, Island of Guam., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 72 (Box 1609)
  - Verso: Mission Home Grounds, Island of Guam: Sixteen hundred miles east of Manila, in the Pacific Ocean, is the island of Guam (gw m). ..., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 72-verso (Box 1609)
  - The Great Geyser Valley, Whakarewarewa, North Island, New Zealand., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 73 (Box 1609)
  - Verso: The Great Geyser Valley, Whakarewarewa, North Island, New Zealand: The great geyser district of New Zealand is the southern part of, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 73-verso (Box 1609)
  - Mount Elliot and Jervois Glacier, from McKinnon's Pass (6,200 ft.), New Zealand., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 74 (Box 1609)
  - Verso: Mount Elliot and Jervois Glacier, from McKinnon's Pass, New Zealand: We are now in New Zealand's Fjordland National Park, the wild, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 74-verso (Box 1609)
  - Across Milford Sound, a Fjord-like Bay between Mountain Walls, W. Coast of New Zealand., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 75 (Box 1609)
  - Verso: Across Milford Sound, West Coast of New Zealand: In this region, the Southern Alps, which line the entire west coast of South Island, rear, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 75-verso (Box 1609)
  - Farms and Fields in the Derwent Valley, Tasmania., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 76 (Box 1609)
  - Verso: Farms and Fields in the Derwent Valley, Tasmania: If you will take your Keystone map slide of Australia and the islands of the Pacific, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 76-verso (Box 1609)
  - Kangaroos in Their Homeland A Scene in the Zoological Garden, Adelaide, South Australia., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 77 (Box 1609)
  - Verso: Kangaroos in Zoological Garden, Adelaide, South Australia: Here you see the strangest animals in the world. They are kangaroos. As some, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 77-verso (Box 1609)
  - Great Eucalyptus or Gum Tree 400 feet High, Australia., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 78 (Box 1609)
  - Verso: Giant Eucalyptus Trees, Victoria: Americans are so used to thinking of the big trees of California as the largest trees in the world, that, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 78-verso (Box 1609)
  - Melbourne, Australia, Looking towards the Southeast from the Exhibition Dome., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 79 (Box 1609)
  - Verso: Melbourne, Australia, from the Exhibition Dome: Melbourne, the capital of Victoria, is the second city in size in the Commonwealth of, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 79-verso (Box 1609)
  - Snow-capped Peaks from Mount Buffalo, Victoria, Australia., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 80 (Box 1609)
  - Verso: Snow-capped Peaks from Mount Buffalo, Victoria, Australia: We are standing on Mount Buffalo in northwestern Victoria, looking east, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 80-verso (Box 1609)
  - A Curious Formation Torpedo Rock, Mount Buffalo, Victoria, Australia., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 81 (Box 1609)
  - Verso: Torpedo Rock, Mount Buffalo, Victoria, Australia: Torpedo rock is another peculiar feature of rock formation. Notice the rounded form, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 81-verso (Box 1609)
  - The Fairy's Grotto, Yarrangobilly, New South Wales, Australia., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 82 (Box 1609)
  - Verso: The Fairy's Grotto, Yarrangobilly, New South Wales: Caves have always been places of mystery and interest wherever found. They were, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 82-verso (Box 1609)
  - Magnificent Harbor of Sydney, Australia., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 83 (Box 1609)
  - Verso: Port Jackson, with the City of Sydney in the Distance, Australia: Sydney is the largest city in Australia. It is the capital of New South Wales, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 83-verso (Box 1609)
  - Sheep on the Range, Queensland, Australia., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 84 (Box 1609)
  - Verso: Sheep on Range, Queensland: No part of the world is better suited to sheep raising than Australia. In the interior are grassy plains much, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 84-verso (Box 1609)
  - In Southern Pacific Waters Natives of New Guinea in their Picturesque Sailing Craft., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 85 (Box 1609)
  - Verso: Natives of New Guinea in Picturesque Sailing Craft: The canoes vary in different districts. Near Port Moresby two or three canoes are tied, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 85-verso (Box 1609)
  - Impressive Magnificence of a Volcanic Eruption in Java, Dutch East Indies., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 86 (Box 1609)
  - Verso: A Volcanic Eruption in Java: Any opening in the earth that throws up hot rock and steam is a volcano. Usually a volcano builds up a cone-shaped, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 86-verso (Box 1609)
  - Immense Trees Bordering an Avenue in Buitenzorg, Java., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 87 (Box 1609)
  - Verso: Canary Tree Avenue, Buitenzorg, Java: The tropical island of Java has a large population of 727 people to the square mile, and with an area, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 87-verso (Box 1609)
  - A Native Porter Laden with Durians, One of the Finest Fruits of the East, Java, Dutch East Indies., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 88 (Box 1609)
  - Verso: Native Porter Laden with Durians, one of Finest Fruits of the East: We are now in one of the most fertile, one of the most beautiful and, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 88-verso (Box 1609)
  - A Tropical Paradise the Eden-like Island of Java, Dutch East Indies., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 89 (Box 1609)
  - Verso: A Tropical Paradise the Eden-like Island of Java: This whole view from mountains of considerable height gives the appearance of a, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 89-verso (Box 1609)
  - The Radiant Splendor of an Equatorial Sunrise off the Coast of Java, Dutch East Indies., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 90 (Box 1609)
  - Verso: An Equatorial Sunrise off Coast of Java: Seldom is it given the traveler to see such glorious cloud effects as those in the scene before us., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 90-verso (Box 1609)
  - Bamboo Water Tanks, Island of Midanao, Philippine Islands., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 91 (Box 1609)
  - Verso: Filipinos of Mindanao Carrying Water in Bamboo tanks, P. I.: These small, brown people with their pleasant, round faces, are natives of, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 91-verso (Box 1609)
  - Mayon, the Peerless Cone of Southern Luzon, Showing Old Spanish Stone Bridge at Legaspi, P. I., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 92 (Box 1609)
  - Verso: Mayon, the Peerless Cone, Shwoing Old Spanish Stone Bridge at Legaspi, P. I.: The Mayon volcano in Albay province, near the sea, is the, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 92-verso (Box 1609)
  - Husking Coconuts Familiar Scene in the Great Coconut Country near Pagsanhan, Island of Luzon, P. I., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 93 (Box 1609)
  - Verso: Husking Coconuts, near Pagsanjan, Island of Luzon, P. I.:The common coconut (Cocos nucifera l.) is found all round the world within the, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 93-verso (Box 1609)
  - Threshing Out Rice with Carabao, Pangasinan Province, Island of Luzon, P. I., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 94 (Box 1609)
  - Verso: Threshing Out Rice with Carabao, Pangasinan Province, Island of Luzon, P. I.: Threshing grain by tramping it out with the feet of domestic, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 94-verso (Box 1609)
  - Filipino "Tractors" at Work Harrowing the Flooded Rice Fields near Manila, P. I., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 95 (Box 1609)
  - Verso: Harrowing the Flooded Rice Fields near Manila, P. I.: This is an altogether Philippine scene. Everything in it belongs to these Islands, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 95-verso (Box 1609)
  - Cascoes on the Pasig River, Manila, P. I., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 96 (Box 1609)